(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
Sakura Mirage
ReGLOSS MINI LIVE
2025.03.30 (SUN) 20:00 --- Start
#ReGLOSS3Dライブ
#ReGLOSS3DLive
瞬間ハートビート
作詞: OHTORA 作曲: OHTORA / maeshima soshi
編曲: maeshima soshi
Shunkan Heartbeat
Lyrics: OHTORA / Composition: OHTORA, maeshima soshi
Arrangement: maeshima soshi
漠然と Step up, Van!
Vaguely stepping up, Van!
欲していたい Fan!
Wanting to be a fan!
日常に違和感
A sense of discomfort in daily life
うんざりしていた
I was getting sick of it
見慣れたり 聞いたりの 眺め
Scenes I've seen and heard so often
理屈を超える 変化を求めていた
I was seeking a change that defies logic
窮屈で 退屈な 日々の中
In the middle of cramped and boring days
突然 君が現れた
Suddenly, you appeared
全身の細胞 駆け巡るように
Like racing through every cell in my body
走り出した 未完成なストーリー
An incomplete story has started to run
モノクロだった 景色が今
The scenery that used to be monochrome
君と出会い カラフルに彩る 万有
Met you and colored the universe colorfully
心 奪われて
My heart was stolen away
気まぐれな 瞬間ハートビート
A whimsical, momentary heartbeat
ドラマチックな 狭間
In a dramatic interval
もう一人じゃない
I'm not alone anymore
きらめく 星
A twinkling star
描く 未来 予想図は
The blueprint of the future I draw
同じ 夢を 引き寄せたいの
I want to pull in the same dream
果てしない 旅路の 向こうで
Beyond the endless journey
鳴り止まない ロマンが 待っている
An unceasing romance is waiting
刻んだ 時には Make it
Make it in the time we've carved
Can't be without you
いつまでも 君と 一緒なら
As long as I'm with you forever
ここから先 広がる 宇宙
The universe spreading out from here on
晴れ渡る 空 飛び出して
Fly out into the clear sky
気分は 上々 想像 以上
Feeling great, beyond imagination
貴重な 黒は 終わりに して
Put an end to the precious black
すべて 叶え あおぞらごと
Grant it all, along with the blue sky
時計の 針が 回り 回る
The hands of the clock turn and turn
限られた 瞬間
Limited moments
...あど時のなかで
...within that time,
鮮やかに Dancing time
vividly dancing time.
心奪われた
My heart was stolen by
気まぐれな瞬間ハートビート
a fickle instant heartbeat.
揺らぐ地球の狭間
In the gap of the swaying earth,
もう一人じゃない煌めく星
I'm no longer alone, a sparkling star.
描く未来予想は
My vision for the future
同じ夢を引き寄せたいよ
is to draw in the same dream.
果てしない旅路の向こうに
Beyond the endless journey,
紛れもない奇跡があるはず
there must be an unmistakable miracle.
さよなら　ラララ　ララバイ
Goodbye, la la la lullaby.
止められはしないこの衝動
I can't stop this impulse,
突き進むだけさ
I'll just keep pushing forward.
なりふり構わず Are you ready?
Regardless of appearance, are you ready?
限界はないさ　自由の無限大の異次元
There are no limits, it's an infinite dimension of freedom.
散りばめた煌めき　空　皆聞いて
With scattered sparkles, everyone in the sky, listen!
喜びも悲しみも分かち合って
Sharing both joy and sorrow,
僕たちならどこまでも
we can go anywhere.
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
いつものやつやるよ！
Let's do our usual thing!
Reach up, We are ReGLOSS!
イェーイ！すごい歓声！
Yay! What an amazing roar from the crowd!
ありがとうー！
Thank you—!
じゃあ、みんなお水も飲みながらだけど
Alright, everyone can take a water break...
自己紹介いつもの順番でよろしく！
...but let's do introductions in the usual order!
おーい！
Okay!
ぇ、そしたら奏からいきます！
Uh, then I'll start, I'm Kanade!
ドレミファソラシド...
Do Re Mi Fa So La Ti Do...
ホロライブデバイス ReGLOSS の...
From Hololive DEV_IS ReGLOSS...
...轟奏でーす！
...it's Todoroki Kanade!
イェーイ！見て見て！
Yay! Look, look!
あ、これ見て見て！髪の毛がすごいな！
Ah, look at this! My hair is amazing!
おおー！すげー！
Whoa! Incredible!
足してー！
And next—!
可愛いポジティブ・ジーニアス！
Cute Positive Genius!
ホロライブデバイス ReGLOSS の一条莉々華だよ！
It's Ichijou Ririka from Hololive DEV_IS ReGLOSS!
まためちゃくちゃ緊張してます！
I'm super nervous again!
うわー！
Whoa!
めっちゃ走ってた。
You were totally rushing.
元気やな。
You're so energetic.
そして、こちら！
And next up!
はい、えー、ホロライブデバイス ReGLOSS の...
Yes, uh, from Hololive DEV_IS ReGLOSS...
...理・垢・儒・ネタ・お君担当...
...the rep for Science, Art, Confucianism, Jokes, and Okun-kun...
...儒富亭らでんでございます！
...it's Juufuutei Raden!
皆さん、楽しんでますかー？
Is everyone having a good time?
そしてー！
And next—!
ブンブンブン！ホロライブデバイス...
Bum bum bum! From Hololive DEV_IS...
...ReGLOSS の番長、火威青...
...it's the ReGLOSS boss, Todoroki Hajime!
イェーイ！
Yay!
集まってくれてありがとない！
Thanks for coming out!
イェーイ！ありがとう！
Yay! Thank you!
さて、先日発表がありました通り...
Now, as announced the other day...
青君は現在活動休止しているため...
...since Ao-kun is currently on hiatus...
今回のミニライブは青君の分も...
...I'll do my absolute best in this mini-live...
...より精一杯頑張りたいと思います！
...including Ao-kun's share!
頑張るぞー！
Let's do this!
ちなみに最初の曲「瞬間ハートビート」だったけどさ...
By the way, the first song was 'Shunkan Heartbeat'...
この曲はもう Hiro Me Countdown でも今回で3回目でしょう？
...this was its 3rd performance, including 'Hiro Me Countdown', right?
まあ莉々華的には、まあまあまあ緊張も...
Well, as for me, my nervousness...
...ちょっと落ち着いてきたかなって感じなんだけど。
...has finally started to settle down a bit.
やったー！一番緊張してたじゃん！
Liar! You were the most nervous of all!
でも奏も実は緊張してました！
Actually, I was nervous too!
緊張してる！慣れないもんですね。
I'm nervous! You never really get used to it.
こういうもんですね、こういうもんは。
That's just the way these things go, I guess.
ねえ。お二人はどう？
Yeah. How about you two?
番長はどう？
How about you, Boss?
なんか、たのちくパフォーマンスできたなって思います！
I feel like I was able to give a fun performance!
イェーイ！
Yay!
番長もやっぱなんか...
Boss, you also, like...
...前回、前々回よりやっぱ...
...more so than the last time or the time before...
...どんどん揃ってきてる！
...your movements are getting more and more in sync!
本当にそう思う。
I really think so too.
角度とかね。
The angles and everything.
色々ね。
All sorts of things.
莉々華ね、ファンがね...
Ririka, look at the fans...
...ほら、綺麗じゃない！
...see, aren't they beautiful!
完璧だー！
They're perfect!
どんどんすごくなるね。
It's getting more and more incredible.
らでんちゃんはどうだった？
How about you, Raden-chan?
いやーでも、本当に楽しいし...
Oh, it's really fun...
...このコメントの皆様も、応援見えておりますよ！
...and I can see everyone's supportive comments!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
「瞬間ハートビート」の前に...
Before 'Shunkan Heartbeat'...
...まさかの我々ヘリコプターに乗って登場しましたけど...
...we unexpectedly made our entrance via helicopter...
...あれ乗ってる間、私これ酔って...
...and while riding it, I was worried about getting motion sick...
...歌えなかったらどうしようと思いながら...
...and not being able to sing...
...ずっと揺られながら。
...as I was being shaken around.
無事でした！よかった！
But I was fine! Thank goodness!
よかったね。
That's good.
しかも COVER 社の一番上っていうね！
And we were on the very top of the COVER building!
すごいね、こんなところがあったなんて。
Amazing, I didn't know a place like this existed.
60階もあるんだ！
It's 60 floors high!
お天気にも恵まれね。
We were also blessed with great weather.
晴天で絶好のライブ日和！
Clear skies and perfect weather for a live performance!
綺麗、晴天。
It's beautiful, clear skies.
今日はね、ReGLOSS の新曲である...
Today, our new ReGLOSS song...
...「サクラミラージュ」のお披露目を兼ねたライブです！
...is being premiered in this live performance!
凄かったよねー！
That was amazing!
どうですか？
How was it?
おー、熱い！
Oh, it's hot!
ちょっとラグがあるね。
There's a bit of a lag.
あるね。でもね、嬉しいね。
There is. But I'm happy.
ちょっと予想して打ってね、みんな。
Try to predict and type it in the chat, everyone.
五三なよ！イェーイ！
Don't slack off! Yay!
そしてね、ライブの感想はハッシュタグ...
And, for your impressions of the live, use the hashtag...
今この上にも出てると思うんですけど、
I think it's appearing above us right now,
リグロス3Dライブでいっぱいポストしていただければと思います！
#ReGLOSS3DLive — please post a lot using it!
よろしくお願いします！
Please support us!
今日ね、お天気にも恵まれましたが...
Today, we were blessed with good weather, but...
なんかちょっといつもよりさらにカメラ綺麗だと思いませんか？皆さん！
Don't you think the camera is even more beautiful than usual? Everyone!
らでんちゃん痩せた？
Raden-chan, did you lose weight?
いや、そういうことじゃない。そういうことじゃないか。
No, that's not it. That's not what it is.
いや、これね。
No, it's this.
しかもイヤモニ、ですよ！
And the in-ear monitors!
イヤモニ！イヤモニかにゃん！
In-ear monitors! In-ear monitors!
じゃじゃじゃん！これ各々のね、ちょっとカラーで...
Ta-da! These are each of our colors...
以前作った動画も上がったと思うんですけど、
I think the video we made previously is also up,
それをつけてやっています！
and we're wearing them for this!
ちなみに今日ステージの演出もすごいらしくて。
By the way, I heard the stage effects today are also amazing.
えー！
Wow!
番長、いつものお願いします！
Bancho, please do the usual!
まあまあ、克ちときな。
Well, well, brace yourself.
お、何？
Oh, what's this?
行くぜ！ファイヤー！！ボォー！
Here we go! FIRE!! Whoosh!
あつい！あついきゃー！
Hot! So hot!
「スパークラー」出して。
Release the "Sparklers."
何つった？
What did you say?
スパークラーだよ。
I said sparklers.
何でカタコトなん？
Why are you speaking so stiffly?
知ってる知ってる、知ってるよ。
I know, I know, I know.
行け！スパークラー！！ジャン！
Go! Sparklers!! Bam!
おー！あー！今回は綺麗！
Oh! Wow! This time they're beautiful!
これね、これこれ。知ってた知ってた。
These ones, these. I knew it, I knew it.
はい、という感じでね、ちょっとかなりやってもらいたいところなんだけど...
Right, so as you can see, we've got quite a lot we want to show you...
まだまだいろんな仕掛けはね、ありますので、このあとも皆さん楽しみにしていていただければと思います！
But there are still many more tricks up our sleeves, so please look forward to the rest of the show!
え、ちょっと莉々華 息切れてんだけど。みんなもう歌いける？
Ugh, I'm already out of breath. Is everyone ready to sing?
あ、水、水飲んでくっか。
Oh, let's go drink some water.
水飲んでっから。はい、どうもー。
I'm drinking water. Alright, see ya.
青と莉々華でお送りしま...
Brought to you by Ao and Ririka...
一条莉々華でございます！
I am Ichijou Ririka!
はい、今日はライブということでね。はい！
Yes, we're here for the live show today. Yes!
あれ？曇ってきてない？
Wait, isn't it getting cloudy?
あ、本当だ！本当だ！
Oh, you're right! It is!
お天気が。お天気に恵まれてとか言ってたのに。
The weather... even though we just said we were blessed with good weather.
お前や！お前のせいやぞ！
It's you! It's your fault!
じゃあね、早速歌聴いてもらえればと思います。
Anyway, let's get right into the next songs.
「泡沫メイビー」と「シンメトリー」、2曲続けていきたいと思います。
We'll be performing "Utakata Maybe" and "Symmetry" back-to-back.
よし、じゃあみんな...
Alright, everyone...
ヤバい、ドキドキしてきた。ゲタゲタ...
Oh no, I'm getting nervous. *Nervous noises*
絶対に緊張するから。
I'm definitely going to be nervous.
それじゃ行きましょうか。
Well then, shall we begin?
聴いてください。泡沫メイビー。
Please listen. Utakata Maybe.
泡沫メイビー
作詞: OHTORA 作曲: OHTORA / maeshima soshi 編曲: maeshima soshi
Utakata Maybe
Lyrics: OHTORA Composition: OHTORA / maeshima soshi Arrangement: maeshima soshi
新しい眩暈みたいな静けさ
A quietness like a new dizziness
触れた温度は
The temperature I touched
またアンニュイ
Is ennui again
一喜一憂しすぎたユーレカ
Eureka, who was too much of a roller coaster of emotions
尽きるまでは
Until it runs out
覚めない探究心
The inquisitiveness that doesn't wake up
立ち止まれば目の前には
If I stop, right in front of me
振り返った時の自分がいて
Is the me from when I looked back
ここで囁くシルエット
A silhouette whispering here
ぼやけて何も聞こえないフレッシュ
Blurry and I can't hear anything, fresh
泡沫メイビー
Utakata Maybe
回れ右　今夜分かれ道
About face, tonight is a fork in the road
紫騒ぎ根に
At the root of the purple bustle
繰り返しさよなら溜息
Repeating goodbye, a sigh
ほんのちょっとの間の停滞
A stagnation for just a little while
霞んだままの停滞を
Stagnation that remains hazy
失った過去も少し停滞
Even the lost past stagnates a bit
今はまだ見過ごしていたいよ
I want to overlook it for now
空が白んで　眩蓋揺らした
The sky turned white and shook the lids
あと一つ何かが足りないな
One more thing is missing
十点満点 Everyday
Perfect 10 every day
It's better to stay 掌の上
It's better to stay on the palm of the hand
徒蒔きのリバイタリティ
Vitality of idle sowing
いつも記憶が愛らしい
The memories are always lovely
ぺてんのような日々の欠片
Fragments of days like a fraud
散らばった地を序して
Ordering the scattered ground
ずっとせっかちで急かされていて
Always being impatient and rushed
雲隠れしたバイブきた
The vibe that went into hiding came
メイビー
Maybe
まわれ右 今夜は分かれ道
About-face, tonight is the crossroads
胸騒ぎ 泡沫メイビー
Heart pounding, Utakata Maybe
繰り返しさよなら溜息
Repeating goodbyes and sighs
しびれるような真昼明けは
After the electrifying noon
ただじっと待っている Day & Night
Just waiting still, Day & Night
雲と雲の切れ間から
From between the clouds
Rays of light shining
まわる後ろを振り返らないで
Don't look back at the spinning rear
そう呟いたんだ
That's what I whispered
シンメトリー
Symmetry
ざわめく街の喧騒
The hustle and bustle of the noisy city
かき消すように弦を弾いて
Strumming the strings as if to drown it out
一心不乱に叫ぶ Go Go
Shouting single-mindedly, Go Go
割れた爪を眺めてる暇もないよ
No time to even look at broken nails
時の流れに飲み込まれたって
Even if swallowed by the flow of time
立ちふさがる壁に真っ向から向かい打とう
Let's face the standing wall head-on
万年未完成磨き続ければ マスターピース
Forever incomplete, keep polishing it and it'll be a masterpiece
塗り潰してゆくイタダキ 努力だけは裏切らない
The summit that's being painted over, only effort will not betray you
舞い手の全戦 インスパイア 先制
The dancer's whole war, inspire, first move
枯れてる変電所 ずっとずっと低迷
Withered substation, stagnation all the time
歯車外したド派手な今日
Today, so flashy with the gears removed
静かに灯す青い炎
A blue flame quietly lit
多少強引でもご愛嬌
Even if it's a bit pushy, it's charming
じっと見つめ合って
Staring still at each other
駆け出せ旋律のように 恋い焦がれて先き乱れて
Run like a melody, yearning and blooming wildly
失いかけた夢の 続きを紡いでいこう
Let's spin the continuation of the dream we almost lost
乾いた世界を満たしてメロディ
Fill the parched world, melody
行くよ一心同体
Let's go, as one soul
君と重なるシンメトリー 手繰り寄せ朝日の方へ
Symmetry overlapping with you, pulling towards the sunrise
ほんの微妙なニュアンスの違い
Just a subtle difference in nuance
絶妙なバランスの塩梅で
With an exquisite balance
すべての歯車たちは巧妙に噛み合っている
All the gears are cleverly interlocking
数学より精密な値 迷い込んだ偏ったパラダイム
Value more precise than math, a biased paradigm wandered into
いつも隣り合わせのトライ これもきっと誰かの Another life
A try that's always side-by-side, this must also be someone's Another life
君も未来も信じたい信じたい
I want to believe, want to believe in you and the future
今だけここに拓け
Only now, open up here
迫る終焉の足音 願いごとは儚くとも
Footsteps of the approaching end, even if my wishes are fleeting
始まりの合図一歩 息をひそめて
One step of the signal to start, holding my breath
静寂を切り裂いて 空へ翼はためかせて
Cut through the silence, fluttering wings towards the sky
待ち望む結末に まばたきすらできないよ
To the long-awaited conclusion, I can't even blink
どんな風も傷も悲しみも Vivify
Vivify any wind, wound, or sadness
寄せた火を飛び越え
Jump over the fire we brought together
まっさらな夜明けに秘めた思い もう後戻りはしない
Thoughts hidden in the brand-new dawn, there's no turning back anymore
駆け出せ旋律のように 恋い焦がれて先き乱れて
Run like a melody, yearning and blooming wildly
失いかけた夢の 続きを紡いでいこう
Let's spin the continuation of the dream we almost lost
乾いた世界を満たしてメロディ 行くよ一心同体
Fill the parched world, melody, let's go, as one soul
君と重なるシンメトリー 手繰り寄せ朝日の方へ
Symmetry overlapping with you, pulling towards the sunrise
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
というわけでね、泡沫メイビーそしてシンメトリー聴いていただきました！
So, we just performed Utakata Maybe and Symmetry!
雨が降ってきたからびしょ濡れだ！
It started raining, so I'm soaking wet!
客席のみんな、雨に濡れましたか？
Everyone in the audience, did you get wet in the rain?
すごい！
Amazing!
あとで、あとで！
Later, later!
夕暮れになってる！
It's sunset now!
確かにね。まぁ雨もだけど、いつの間にかこんな素敵な夕暮れになってて。
True. The rain was something, but before we knew it, it became such a wonderful sunset.
ねぇ。めちゃめちゃ綺麗。
Yeah. It's so beautiful.
これ、あの、カメラ引きでごろごろ、あ、気づいたんだけどさ、
When the camera pulled back, I noticed...
ステージのさ、外枠の形が、あのホロライブデバイスのエンターキーのマークなの！
The shape of the outer frame of the stage is the Enter key mark of Hololive DEV_IS!
あ、本当だ！あ、夜になったから分かりやすいけど！
Oh, true! It's easy to see since it's dark now!
確かにな。ライトでね。分かりやすくなったんだ。
Exactly. It became clearer because of the lights.
すげー！
Amazing!
あ、ちゃぷちゃぷするんだよね。これね。
Look, it splashes! It makes a splashing sound.
水が跳ねる！あ、すごい！
The water splashes! Oh, wow!
じゃ、やめて。こんなところで水遊びしないの。まだあるから。まだあるから。
Hey, stop it! No playing with water here. We still have more to do!
やばいやばい。待って待って。水浸しにしないで。
Wait, wait! Don't get everything soaked.
そりゃね。いいんじゃない？歌片メイビーとシンメトリー、3Dお披露目ぶりだって。
That's true. By the way, it's been a while since 'Utakata Maybe' and 'Symmetry' were performed in 3D, right?
ねー。めちゃめちゃ久しぶり。
Yeah. It's been such a long time.
いや、そこまで。まだ一週間いってないから。
Well, not that long. It hasn't even been a week yet.
え、上手くなっちゃったかな。どうでしたか？皆さん。
I wonder if we've improved. What did you think, everyone?
じゃあちょっと水飲んでくる。
I'm going to go drink some water.
いってらっしゃーい。
Take care.
で、今何話してたんだっけ？
Wait, what were we talking about?
あの、シンメトリーと歌片メイビーは3Dお披露目以来だねって話。
We were saying it's the first time since the 3D debut for 'Symmetry' and 'Utakata Maybe'.
そうだよね。でもなんか、もう二曲目、三曲目だからか分かんないけど、ちょっと緊張がほぐれて、
Right. But somehow, by the second or third song, the tension has eased...
今噛みまくってるからダメなんだけどさ。
...though I'm still stumbling over my words right now.
はい。というわけで、次の曲は……
Anyway, the next song is...
あ、まだ番長戻ってきてない。
Wait, Bancho hasn't come back yet.
あ、そういうことね。次の曲について喋ろって。
Oh, I see. Let's talk about the next song first.
わった、わった、わった。わった、わった、わった。
Okay, okay, okay. Okay, okay, okay.
しーちゃん、今10万人が見てる……。
Look, 100,000 people are watching right now!
バカな……！いいの？10万人の前でやることバカめで。
No way! Doing stupid things in front of 100,000 people?
記念に、わっか、ありがとうございました！
To commemorate this, thank you so much!
なになに？新しいミーム？非常口になるよ、もう。
What's that? A new meme? Like an emergency exit.
ハニワかも知れん。びっくりして引いちゃった。
Might be a Haniwa. I was so surprised I pulled back.
ねぇ、サクラミラージュが3Dで初お披露目となるわけだけど、
Well, 'Sakura Mirage' is going to be performed in 3D for the first time...
確かにまだ振り付け見せてないもんね。
...but we haven't shown the choreography yet, have we?
ね。サビ以外はまだみんな知らないからさ。
Yeah, except for the chorus, nobody knows it yet.
ちょっとせっかくだし、この曲のイメージをポーズで表してみない？
Since we're here, why don't we express the image of this song with a pose?
そうだね！いいよ、いいよ、いいよ！
Sure! Good idea!
じゃあ番長からいく？
Shall we start with Bancho?
おっけー。いくじゃ。
Okay. Here I go.
おおー！バレエみたいな。花の妖精さんかな。
Oh! Like a ballet. Are you a flower fairy?
あ、可愛い！あ、桜の妖精のような動きでございました。
Oh, cute! That was a cherry blossom fairy-like movement.
じゃあ次、奏でいきます。
Next, Kanade's turn.
それは何？海苔巻きかな？それワカメだろ、もう。ワカメじゃないの？
What is that? A seaweed roll? That's just seaweed. Isn't that seaweed?
ワカメに引っ張られたね、ワカメりりか。ワカメ奏で。
You got pulled towards the seaweed, Seaweed Ririka. Seaweed Kanade.
はい。いきます。
Alright. My turn.
ぽん！あ、ダイナミック！ダイナミック、ダイナミック！
Bam! Oh, dynamic! Dynamic, dynamic!
すごい飛ぶ！これぐらい飛べるんだぜってところを見せてやりたかった。
So high! I wanted to show how high I can jump.
カメラこっちだった。あ、可愛い。
The camera was over here. Oh, cute.
はい。そして青ちゃん。やっぱりサクラミラージュ。これでしょう。
And then, Ao-chan. For Sakura Mirage, it's gotta be this.
あ、かっちょいー。かっちょいー。かっちょいー。
Oh, stylish. Stylish, stylish.
この四人の中で誰が一番イメージと近かったか、皆さん予想して当ててみてください。
Everyone, guess which one of us four was closest to the image.
それやるんだったら別のやつやるんだった！卑怯だよ！
If we're doing that, I would've done a different one! That's unfair!
真面目にやったんちゃうんか。はい。
Weren't you being serious? Okay.
あ、そんなんじゃ、いきましょうか。いきましょうか。
Well then, shall we go? Shall we?
もうやっちゃうんですか。そんな新曲聴いていただいちゃいますか。
Are we really going to do it? Are we going to let you hear our new song?
シンメトリー？あ、今から、あ、違う違う。シンメトリーじゃないの？
Symmetry? Oh, from now... wait, no. It's not Symmetry?
よし。それでは、新曲聴いてください。サクラミラージュ。
Okay. Please listen to our new song, 'Sakura Mirage'.
Staring to your eyes
Let me feel alive
それは始まりの合図
Are you ready for this?
That's the signal to start
柔らかな風 ほら春めいて
共鳴するわ ふわり
The gentle breeze, look, it's becoming spring-like
Resonating softly
丘をなぞる染める桃色
別れの予感はソメイヨシノ
Pink coloring the contours of the hill
A premonition of parting is the Somei-yoshino
移ろったって変わらず君と
そのコントラスト その余白はいつかのため
Even if things transition, I'll be with you unchanged
That contrast, that blank space is for someday
Save the best for last
時を咲く 震えた指
Blooming through time, trembling fingers
噛みしめまどろみ 熱の向こうへ
解き放て Oh mama
Savoring the slumber, beyond the heat
Release it, Oh mama
見つめた Miracle Miracle
Looking at the miracle, miracle
いついつまでも大好き
I'll love you forever and ever
一切合切もいっさいがっさ
Absolutely everything, and everything
大胆的なラブストーリー
A daring love story
Stay for me
ぼやけてしまいそうな桃源郷
An utopia that seems to be blurring
完璧に描けなくたっていいよ
It's okay if it's not painted perfectly
あれ？
Huh?
もう一回遊べるってこと？
Does this mean we can play again?
ええ！？いいじゃん！遊ぼうぜ！
Eh!? That's great! Let's play!
皆さん生配信でお送りしております。
Everyone, we are broadcasting live.
生配信。それレグラスのいつものやつ。
A live stream. That's the usual ReGLOSS thing.
ちょ、ちょっと待ってくださいね。
Pl-please wait a moment.
もう一回やるからちょっと待ってね。
We'll do it again, so please wait a bit.
もう一回始まるじゃん。
It's starting again.
もう一回アビデできるってこと？
Does that mean we can do ABIDE again?
いやもう一回柔らかな風呼び起こすわ。
I'm going to call forth the gentle breeze again.
ちょっとお待ちくださいね皆さん。
Please wait a moment, everyone.
ちょっと始まり合図失敗しちゃったわ。
I messed up the starting signal a bit.
失敗してないよ。
I didn't mess up.
ワカメやっとく？
Should we do the seaweed dance?
ワカワカメ！
Waka-wakame!
ちょっとだけお待ちください。すみません。
Please wait just a moment. Sorry.
桜と言えばゲームする？
Want to play the 'Speaking of Cherry Blossoms' game?
パンパンって言って。
Say 'clap clap'.
いいよ。じゃあ私からね。
Okay. I'll start.
パンパン、桜餅！
Clap clap, cherry blossom rice cake!
弱い！
Weak!
三人でやって。奏も脱落者として。
The three of you do it. Kanade is disqualified too.
じゃあ番長からね。桜と言えばね。
Okay, starting from Ban-cho. 'Speaking of cherry blossoms...'
パンパン、ビニールシート！
Clap clap, vinyl sheet!
パンパン、お団子！
Clap clap, dango!
お団子。まあいいでしょう。
Dango. Well, I guess that's fine.
パンパン、お弁当！
Clap clap, bento box!
桜と言えばなのそれ？
Is that related to cherry blossoms?
サクラミラージュは！
How about Sakura Mirage!
なんか大喜利大会になってますやん、これ。
This has turned into an improv comedy contest.
お花見行きたいね。
I want to go flower viewing.
でもなんかちょっと桜っぽくない？この色味もピンクがかっててさ。
But doesn't it look a bit like cherry blossoms? This color has a pinkish tint.
わあ、綺麗！めちゃくちゃよけいなのかな？
Wow, so pretty! Is it a bit much?
ペンライトもね。いっぱい振ってくれてます。ありがとう！
The penlights too. Everyone's waving them a lot. Thank you!
ペンライト振ってくれてる人ー！
Everyone waving their penlights!
まあこういうのも生ならではじゃないですか。こういうトラブルがあるっていうのも。
Well, this kind of thing is typical of live broadcasts, isn't it? Having this kind of trouble.
じゃあもう少々お待ちください。
Then please wait a little longer.
ちょっとより可愛くここ歌う練習するわ。
I'll practice singing this part a bit more cutely.
大丈夫よ、今の感じで。
It's fine, just like you did now.
それは始まりの合図も返してね。
Give me the starting signal back, too.
それは始まりのアイス！
That's the starting love!
可愛すぎるんだなんて…思ってたのと違うわ。
Thinking it's too cute... it's different from what I expected.
からの！ Are you ready for this?
And then! Are you ready for this?
Are you ready for this?
で、番長は？
And, how about Ban-cho?
柔らかな風…
A gentle breeze...
奏から見た番長はいつもこうなんだって。
From Kanade's perspective, Ban-cho is always like this.
いつも可愛いって。そういうことね。
Always cute. That's what you mean.
このファンファーレのここ好きなんでね。
I like this part of the fanfare.
ごめん、そこ習ってないからできないわ。
Sorry, I haven't learned that part so I can't do it.
皆次のこれに備えてるもんね。アビデにゃ。
Everyone is preparing for this next part. ABIDE-nya.
一番緊張してるこのアビデだからね。
This ABIDE is what I'm most nervous about.
このラップ長いけん、一回躓いたらもうダメになる。
Because this rap is long, if I stumble once, it's over.
アビデ・ダビデ・アビデ・ダビデ…
ABIDE DABIDE ABIDE DABIDE...
ちょっと1回混ぜてみてみてみて
Wait, let's try mixing it up once.
え、ちょさ、早速なんだけどさ
Eh, wait, it's a bit sudden...
ちょ、さっきのさ、踊った時のさ、ミスの話していい？
Can I talk about the mistake when we were dancing earlier?
あ、いいよ
Oh, sure.
足踏んだよね
You stepped on my foot, right?
え、内緒、内緒、内緒の話
Eh, it's a secret, a secret talk!
そうなの？そうなの？
Is that so? Is that so?
リリカがすっと足を引いちゃった
Ririka just pulled her foot away.
後でみんなアーカイブで見てみてね
Everyone, please check the archive later.
でも全然軽かったから
But it was totally light!
え、気づいてなかったの？気づいてると思ってた
Eh, you didn't notice? I thought you noticed.
気づいてるけど言わなかった。ごめんね
I noticed, but I didn't say anything. Sorry!
あーごめんね
Ah, I'm sorry!
いや、今言ったら面白いかなと思って
No, I just thought it would be funny if I said it now.
ちょっと一緒にお水飲んでこようかな
Maybe I'll go drink some water together with you.
はい。じゃあね。この後みんながお水から戻ってきたら踊りましょう
Alright. Well then, let's dance after everyone returns from drinking water.
そして歌いましょう
And let's sing.
え、リリカも飲まなくて大丈夫？
Eh, Ririka, are you okay not drinking?
あ、飲んどくわ。ちょっと
Ah, I'll drink some. Just a bit.
私も飲んどく
I'll drink some too.
一列になっとく？なっとこ、なっとこ
Shall we line up? Let's, let's.
対称性始まる？
Is the symmetry starting?
やるか、もう一回ね
Shall we do it? One more time.
一番前以外もやってみたいんだよね
I want to try being somewhere other than the very front.
一番前どうしたいの？
What do you want to do at the very front?
なんかうにょうにょうにょって感じ
Like, wiggle wiggle wiggle...
そこまでじゃなかったかな
It wasn't quite that much.
それでは改めてまして、新曲『サクラミラージュ』聴いてください。どうぞ
Then once again, please listen to our new song, 'Sakura Mirage'. Here you go.
サクラミラージュ
Sakura Mirage
Step in to your eye / Make me feel alive
Step into your eye / Make me feel alive
それは始まりの合図
That's the signal of the beginning
Are you ready for this?
柔らかな風 ほら春めいて
Soft breeze, look, it's feeling like spring
共鳴するファンファーレ
The resonating fanfare
臆面もなく染める桃色
Pink coloring without hesitation
別れの予感はソメイヨシノ
Premonition of parting is Someiyoshino
浴びて 浴びて 浴びて 本領発揮
Bathe in it, bathe in it, bathe in it, show your true colors
浴びて Dance with me now
Bathe in it, dance with me now
躍り出した天かわる
The dancing sky changes
君とのコントラスト
Contrast with you
強い白馬はいつかのため
Strong white horse is for someday
Stay Best for Life
時折咲く震えた音
Faltering sounds that occasionally bloom
噛み締めるまだ微熱のウィーアー
Savoring the still slight fever "We are"
飛んでけ Bigger Dive どんなウィーバー
Fly away Bigger Dive, whatever weaver
解き放て On My Mind
Unleash it On My Mind
春が来た さあさ サクラミラージュ
Spring has come, come on, Sakura Mirage
咲いて儚んで笑って Endless
Bloom, be ephemeral, laugh, Endless
揺れながら まだ夢の中さ
Swaying, still in a dream
そっとささやいて 叶えて Step for me
Softly whisper, grant it, Step for me
Make me, Make me, Make me
花開く
Flowers bloom
行き着く暇もない Life is
Life with no time to settle down is
パパパパ パラダイス
Pa-pa-pa-pa Paradise
一世一代の今を愛し合おう
Let's love each other in this once-in-a-lifetime now
花開く
Flowers bloom
大胆不敵なラプソディ
Bold and fearless rhapsody
キラリラビータ
Kirari ra vita
Stay for me
ぼやけてしまいそうな桃源郷
Arcadia that seems like it might blur
完璧に描けなくたっていいや
It's okay even if it can't be drawn perfectly
熱を帯びたまま 込み上げるフィルモア
While heated, the surging 'Fill more'
はらり 刷新だ 中枢へ
Fluttering, it's a renovation to the core
新しい自分を この目でキャッチしよう
Let's catch the new me with these eyes
変わらないものを胸に
With unchanging things in our hearts
歩んでいこう
Let's walk forward
センチメンツ 紡ぐものがたりは Endless
The story woven by sentiments is Endless
Come on now
解き澄ませ 今日までを
Unleash it, everything until today
Carry out Sneaker 羅針盤突き放せ
Carry out Sneaker, push away the compass
咲き誇れ Love for now
Bloom proudly Love for now
春が来た さあさ サクラミラージュ
Spring has come, come on, Sakura Mirage
咲いて儚んで笑って Endless
Bloom, be ephemeral, laugh, Endless
揺れながら まだ夢の中さ
Swaying, still in a dream
そっとささやいて 叶えて Step for me
Softly whisper, grant it, Step for me
Make me, Make me, Make me
花開く
Flowers bloom
行き着く暇もない Life is
Life with no time to settle down is
パパパパ パラダイス
Pa-pa-pa-pa Paradise
一世一代の今を愛し合おう
Let's love each other in this once-in-a-lifetime now
花開く
Flowers bloom
大胆不敵なラプソディ
Bold and fearless rhapsody
キラリラビータ
Kirari ra vita
Stay for me
明日以降が 決まり文句のシナリオよりいい
Better than tomorrow and beyond being a cliché scenario
右往左往しながら 起死回生
Resuscitation while wandering back and forth
トップシステムで 巻き起こす ニューウェーブ
New wave stirred up by the top system
沸き上がれ 人生は無限大
Surge up, life is infinite
Wake up Go! いつだって絶好調
Wake up Go! Always in top form
練り出す シナジー
Churning out synergy
未来 切り開いて 響き合う 鼓動
Beating hearts resonating, carving out the future
ずっと飾らない君でいて
Always be the unadorned you
一対一の温度で 誰かがそよげば
If someone sways with a one-on-one temperature
霞んでもいい 芽吹いてメロディ
It's okay to be hazy, sprout Melody
この鼓動に泳いで恋して
Swim in this heartbeat and fall in love
春が来た さあさ サクラミラージュ
Spring has come, come on, Sakura Mirage
咲いて儚んで笑って Endless
Bloom, be ephemeral, laugh, Endless
揺れながら まだ夢の中さ
Swaying, still in a dream
そっとささやいて 叶えて Step for me
Softly whisper, grant it, Step for me
Make me, Make me, Make me
花開く
Flowers bloom
行き着く暇もない Life is
Life with no time to settle down is
パパパパ パラダイス
Pa-pa-pa-pa Paradise
一世一代の今を愛し合おう
Let's love each other in this once-in-a-lifetime now
花開く
Flowers bloom
大胆不敵なラプソディ
Bold and fearless rhapsody
キラリラビータ
Kirari ra vita
Stay for me
Staring at me, stay for me
ありがとうございましたー！
Thank you very much!
最高！みんな、絶対また会えるよ！
That was great! Everyone, we'll definitely meet again!
幸せー！
I'm so happy!
最高ー！
The best!
写真撮ろ、写真撮ろ！
Let's take a photo, let's take a photo!
ハイ、チーズ！
Say cheese!
思い出に残そ！
Let's preserve this memory!
イエーイ！ピース！
Yay! Peace!
みんな見てくれてありがとねー！
Thanks for watching, everyone!
これすごいよ！ほら花火！
This is amazing! Look, fireworks!
うわあ、花火だー！
Wow, fireworks!
きれーい！
So beautiful!
この後、20時45分から
After this, starting at 20:45,
『サクラミラージュ』のパフォーマンスビデオが
the performance video of 'Sakura Mirage'
プレミア公開されますのでたくさん見てください！
will be premiered, so please watch it a lot!
見てねー！
Please watch it!
45分から！
From 45 past!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
リスナーのみなさん、ありがとうございました！
Everyone in the audience, thank you very much!
またお会いしましょう！
See you again!
ReGLOSS MINI LIVE Sakura Mirage
2025. 03. 30 [SUN] 20:00 Start